export default data = [
  {
      question: "All the new students were given one minute to _____ introduce themselves to the whole class.",
      options: ["briefly","famously","gradually","obviously"],
      correct_option: "briefly"
  },
  {
      question: "His dark brown jacket had holes in the elbows and had _____ to light brown, but he continued to wear it.",
      options: ["cycled","faded","loosened","divided"],
      correct_option: "faded"
  },
  {
      question: "Everyone in our company enjoys working with Jason. He’s got all the qualities that make a _____ partner. ",
      options: ["desirable","comfortable","frequent","hostile"],
      correct_option: "desirable"
  },
  {
      question: "Eyes are sensitive to light. Looking at the sun _____ could damage our eyes. ",
      options: ["hardly","specially","totally","directly"],
      correct_option: "directly"
  },
  {
      question: "We were forced to _____ our plan for the weekend picnic because of the bad weather. ",
      options: ["maintain","record","propose","cancel"],
      correct_option: "cancel"
  },
  {
      question: "Three people are running for mayor. All three _____ seem confident that they will be elected, but we won’t know until the outcome of the election is announced. ",
      options: ["particles","receivers","candidates","containers"],
      correct_option: "candidates"
  },
  {
      question: "If you _____ a traffic law, such as drinking and driving, you may not drive for some time.",
      options: ["destroy","violate","attack","invade"],
      correct_option: "violate"
  },
  {
      question: "Applying to college means sending in applications, writing study plans, and so on. It’s a long _____, and it makes students nervous.",
      options: ["errand","operation","process","display"],
      correct_option: "process"
  },
  {
      question: "Dr. Chu’s speech on the new energy source attracted great _____ from the audience at the conference.",
      options: ["attention","fortune","solution","influence"],
      correct_option: "attention"
  },
  {
      question: "Everyone in the office must attend the meeting tomorrow. There are no _____ allowed.",
      options: ["exceptions","additions","divisions","measures"],
      correct_option: "exceptions"
  },
  {
      question: "To make fresh lemonade, cut the lemon in half, _____ the juice into a bowl, and then add as much water and sugar as you like.",
      options: ["decrease","squeeze","freeze","cease"],
      correct_option: "squeeze"
  },
  {
      question: "Buddhism is the _____ religion in Thailand, with 90% of the total population identified as Buddhists.",
      options: ["racial","competitive","modest","dominant"],
      correct_option: "dominant"
  },
  {
      question: "When I open a book, I look first at the table of ______ to get a general idea of the book and to see which chapters I might be interested in reading.",
      options: ["contracts","contents","contests","contacts"],
      correct_option: "contents"
  },
  {
      question: "The children were so _____ to see the clown appear on stage that they laughed, screamed, and clapped their hands happily. ",
      options: ["admirable","fearful","delighted","intense"],
      correct_option: "delighted"
  },
  {
      question: "Typhoon Maggie brought to I-lan County a huge amount of rainfall, much greater than the _____ rainfall of the season in the area. ",
      options: ["average","considerate","promising","enjoyable"],
      correct_option: "average"
  },
]
